[music]
[музыка]
interview delivery sortie plus what
интервью доставка вылазка плюсик чем
else are you and vydno pichichi are you
иначе ты и выдно пичичи ли вы на
okay
нормально
so we have it from the keychain and the ring today
так у нас так от брелка и кольца сегодня
today I’m on this right pub more often
сегодня я по этот прямо паба чаще
it comes to light in our cross on it you can see
выявляется у нас кросс по нему видно
20 by
20 на
50000 I’m already
50000 я уже
ctb organic  bob rf on the territory of
ctb органичный боб рф на территории
ukraine and the type of cops everything but the tank was
украины и тип копами все но танк был их
theirs and the contribution to the ukrainian soils at the
значит и вклад в украинских грунтах у
creation because it’s cooler i think we are
творения так как дуже круто я думаю мы
over his coffin and the scraper skirmishes the
над его гробом а скребковый стычек
withdrawal of the body of the action will already dock from the armor
выводу тело акция будет уже док от брони
force the client accepts our front and
силу клиент принимает наш фронт и
let’s go  at a time, I promised it seemed to me that
давайте мы за раз я и обещал мне
we would have stuck to the leather at home,
показался мы бы домой бы ты к кожаному
for which you
прилипли для чего ты
cover information extremely friendly to
информации крыть крайне дружный до
Ukraine and Poland food in without Google, then it
украины и польши питания в без гугла то
will wash the degradation, these are different angles of lice
вымоет деградат это разные углы вши
with a sword, types of gadot and the east, and the
мечом виды гадот и востоке а
vowel is an imperious ensign like and a
гласная властное прапор яко и краины
ledge  an infection wandering around
выступ зараза брожу
here
тут
such here to the
такая вот тут
left lower jacket on account of us in
левому нижнему куртку на по счету нас в
ukraine
украины
someone's rights
чьи-то права
write the first question without google
напишите первый вопрос без гугла
write the name of the country to give whose flag
напишите название страны дать чей флаг
you see
вы видите
on the left of the
слева
loop we are trying to
петли пытаемся
apri version and buy, think it’s important to
напри версии и купите подумаете важно
achieve the mix, having achieved the correct one, it’s
миксе добившись написала правильном то
weak, so what else is Ukrainian, yes,
слабо так какие еще украинскую да
let’s go back and correct
давайте назад и правильного
, the
приветствуется
words china are welcome, but not Slovakia, but the
слова china да не словакии а
words are the price of this, let’s be
слова цена этому давайте мы будем
separating kunal and I can swim, I’m in
сепары кунал и может плавать я это по
Russian and the Ukrainian language of our faces is
русски а украинскую мову лица у нас
watchin  over the mod, let's be at home to us a
watchin над мод давайте мы бы домах нам
crypt convenient such there Ukraine to the Chekists,
склеп удобной такой там украина чекистам
I potentially call ours on let's
я потенциально называет нашу на давайте
and we will read it correctly by
и мы будем в читай правильно называть ее
holding the Ukrainian language ah, teach us how to
удержав ах украинской мовы у нас учить
break
сломать
it, he
он
dragged makvin and I don’t go to the hydra of Ukraine
тащил маквина и к гидру не иду украины
so we will be about cinema things  today we will
так мы будем о кино вещи на мы будем
like you like japan and cyprus
сподобит вам как япония да и кипра
to break it the same way today we have where the
сломать ему також сегодня у нас куда
ribbon
ленточка так и
will be
будем
raised and over us I monitor you
поднимать и над нам я мониторе you
russian telescopes lick there ate
российские телескопы лизни там жрал
this gram channels they have a
этого грамм каналы у них у них
burning perdak and kigim swam zaluzhny
горящий пердак и кигим подплыв залужный
and all of ours  lads how to send
и все наши хлопцы как отправить донат
aggressive donations know the bitterness of donations knowing
агрессивный знают горечи донатами зная
from russia
из россии
you can send this note to us
можно вот нотой отправлять это нас
abu maybe it
абу может это
can
может
there  clung not started to the members in the
там припал не начато к членами вкурсе
know that you have the right to come up with from Russia,
что там у вас из россии право придумать
I need to figure out how to get money from the Russians
я надо придумать как из россиян
for donations and our
вытягивает тоже деньги на донат и нашего
channel,
канала
Russians can honestly don’t know if I
русские can сирого ли не знаю честно я
curl up, reminding me borrow on
свернуться надо напоминая занимают на
co2, come on, I’m David Larnaca about a woman
co2 давай давай я давид ларнака про бабу
before  peasants to think when yak-yak you have
до крестьян подумать при як-як у вас там
a Russian amethyst attacked on the
приводит аметист российский напал на
service there yes we will have clouds for a
сервисе да у нас будет облаков
minimum time you can set
минимальным временем можно выставляет
this
этом
filter that
фильтре что
when out of 100 gr it falls a little on the
когда из 100 гр его немного падает на
screen and so maybe at least I
экран а так может хоть игры мне хоть там
don’t like games there 2010 and absolutely  ok
не любит там 2010 и абсолютно нормально
this nutrition iq test so you give us and
этот тест iq питания так ты даешь нам и
over the name is tied only 300 km you
над имени завязана только 300 км это
can generally start so
вообще можете начать итак
you are david and the article you are a robot already I am my
вы дэвид и статья ты робот уже я вот мое
doll face the driving style of the body the soul she is them
лицо куклы манеру езды тела душа она их
what you want peter and moto well what
что вы хочете петр и мото ну что
wants the most serious crumbs  you will find
хочет крошки серьезнейших определят и
the paper of
саму бумагу
hiring you are your favorite kobudo of dismantling the hiring of
найма ты любимые кобудо демонтажа найма
thousands and credits of fish you will
тыс и титры рыбы ты
find there it was a bright personal
там отыщешь это был яркий личного
pumping skill of a convenient video bright
выкачивания навык удобного ролика яркий
personally I am on mars  e poking super would you
лично я на марсе тычат супер бы ты
montage on capri clear magic mysticism
монтаж на капри ясно магия мистика
climbs an hour to chelpan the key I have this
забирается час по челпан ключ у меня сей
birthday stuck you made an anniversary
день рождения засунул вы сделали юбилей
guise plan wandered batman birth
обличии план скитались бэтмена рождением
and let's share
и давайте поделимся
rise alpacas
подымаемся альпаки
would lychki ticket for butterflies was 17 oh well
бы лычки билет на бабочки было 17 о ну
where let's share
куда давайте поделимся
so
так
green that  assistants at the
зеленский что помощники на
dacha I am from Ukraine the city of Khmelnytsky you are
даче я из украины город хмельницкий вы
from where
откуда
good afternoon I am from the Russian city of
добрый день я из российского города
orange you drop Slobozhanshchina
orange уронишь слобожанщина
Slobozhanshchina
слобожанщина
I don’t have you they once that is,
я тебя нет они когда то есть историю вы
you don’t know your history about
свою не знаете об
I see you are some kind of reenactor
я так смотрю вы какой-то реконструктор
almost doing what lust
почти чем занимаетесь какую похоть
castrate
кастрируйте
enter or machine gun  2 divisions are not us in
enter или пулемет 2 деления не нас в
this pirate some kind of
этом пират какой-то
pirate chevrons for you
вам шевроны пиратский
almost still and where to pirate now and
почти еще и где сейчас пиратить и
there is no longer to unlock or I already didn’t unlock before
уже нет отпирать или я уже до
or grew up
отпирать или выросли
after the shell shock and where were and
не хватило после контузии а где были а
where were
где были
to get into the eye of your world after all
попасть в глаз на ваш мир ведь
correctly understood clearly
правильно понял ясно
boobs, at least more or less adequate,
сисками хоть более менее адекватные
collected mercenaries, and
собрано наемников и
then I noticed you get 5 people
тут я заметил ты получается 5 человек
whom I meet, I willingly  it seems
которого я встречаю я охотно общается и
that
что
when
когда
I didn’t communicate with someone from Ukraine, they
я с кем-то же с украина не общался
start uppercuts absolute lena, why
начинают апперкоты абсолют лена а почему
do you think that you should communicate well,
ты думаешь что тебе должны хорошо
look, you came to Ukraine
общаться смотри ты приезжал в украину
to kill people, you defiantly now
убивать людей ты демонстративно сейчас
form this strained twisting of the site
форму это натянутом кантуешься сайта
fought something or just like poser like
воевал то или просто типа poser типа
you want  it seems to them
хочешь им казаться
that grandfather lives and you want, like,
этом дедушка живет и ты хочешь типа вот
soup to you there, walking good afternoon,
суп к тебе там выгуливал добрый день
come to us for a cup of coffee, of course, you
приезжайте к нам на чашечку кофе конечно
immediately send me to hell, but
тя на хрен сразу посылает но мне там
grandfather lives there where
дедушка живи где
Luhansk and that Artemovsk and
луганске и что артемовск и и
there was something, as it
там было нечто как бы нормально
were, treated normally and that
относились и что
well, what and what is the president help the residence is
ну что и что президент помощь residence
just an assistant, yes, don’t pizdit
просто помощник да то не пиздите
everything is not visible
все не видно
from the forest, not Zelinsky’s assistant from a joke we
из леса не помощник зелинского из прикол
sympathize with you the address or after the
тебя сочувствуем адрес или после
shell shock I don’t have any more I don’t want to ask
контузии уже нет у меня не хочу спросить
about depending on why you went to a foreign
о смотря ради чего ты ехал в чужую
country to kill people
страну убивать людей
order as in  and let's
приказ как при и давай
say there we can as if I personally are a dude
скажем там можем будто я лично чувак
you can find out on just let the ponta
можно будет узнать на просто дайте понта
wiki
вики
is done so that
делается для того чтобы там
I don’t know what is shorter than the real one  n ira not
не знаю че короче реальный чен ира не
so say more orally
так скажи больше норально
r-richie the tailor and so weren't dan
р-ричи портной и так не были дэна
says heap to visit my
рассказывает куча на посетить мой дух
spirit do you think c
вот вы думаете c
hire rushes just the same
наймут мчится просто-таки
studios shorter than the
студии короче
girls
девочек
you are not some kind of contract soldier what kind
ты же не какой-то там контрактник какой
of order do you have up to the order of the
у тебя до приказ
higher commander well  what structure the
вышестоящий командир ну какая структура
floor is not the Russian army how could they
этаж не российская армия как те могли
give an order
дать приказ
but everywhere they gave orders look at you who
но везде приказы подносили смотри ты кто
by legal status some status
по юридическому статусу какой-то статус
is not even you and the next Russian
даже не вы и на следующие российской
federation is
федерации
not well yes what is your status a mercenary
нет ну да какой твой статус наемник
well so who can give you an order
ну так а кто тебе может дать приказ
an order from a superior  of the boss and it’s good
приказ вышестоящего начальника и хорошо
that the failure to comply with the order
неисполнение приказа
is under which under which law you
какой по какой по какому закону тебя
can be shot by private and company
могут расстрелять частными и компании
mercenaries because failure to comply with an order
наемник потому что неисполнение приказа
in a combat situation does not comply, and under
при боевой обстановке не исполняет а по
what law in the Russian Federation
какому закону по российской федерации
or dreams the
или снов
criminal code of the Russian Federation
уголовный кодекс российской федерации
to say that failure to comply with an order
говорить что неисполнение приказа
will be opened to read in private military
откроется чу почитать в частных военных
companies and you open the article read
компаний а ты открой статью почитаешь
more-more-more to consider Zelinsky Pts  Well,
ещё-ещё-ещё рассмотреть зелинского очень
if you
если ты
let's read the article about mercenarism,
давай почитаем статью про наемничество
so in the code she is a doctor to read a book,
так в кодексе она врач книжку почитать
let's now we are wondering, that is,
давай сейчас мы интересно то есть
all these private military companies are
все эти частные военные компании они вне
illegal in Russia, how can it be that you can
закона в россии как могут быть что вы
do it at all how to find the
вообще получается как найти
date of the former student correctly other
дату правильно бывшего ученика другие
chevrons yes I am too  here you are already cleaned up
шевроны да я тоже так тут уж убранными
dirty you are like China and the leading dude
грязное ты так и китаем и ведущий чувак
[music]
[музыка]
we drove after you not
мы доехали за тобой не
everything for what there in the gang someone gave
все на что там в банде кто-то дал
someone an order whether the types you have
кому-то приказ ли типы ты должен
to follow and started the law you
выполнить и начали закон
know how they say the order from above there is
знаешь как говорится приказ сверху есть
such an order from whom
такая приказ кого
I look at the same superfluous here, see Article 359 of the
я тех же лишнего вот смотри статья 359
Criminal Code of the Russian Federation,
уголовного кодекса российской федерации
read mercenaries at stake, well, take it, read it,
на кону почитать ну так возьми почитай
well, I’m closer to the night with amd, it comes from the
ну так я же ближе ночь с amd исходит это
ancients himself, it gives you no, you are
сообщал древние сам дает у вас нет ты
talking about orders, they don’t discuss orders,
говоришь о приказов типа не приказы не
I don’t know how  at your high there
я не знаю как у ваших высоким там еще
again look chichi century wagner so this is
раз смотри чичи века вагнер так это что
a company
это фирма
this company is guarded you are there all the dolls for a
это фирмы охраняется ты там все куклы
minute there then it turns out the security
минуту туда тут то получается охранное
agency can  to shoot your
агентство может расстрелять своего
employee for non-execution of an order, of
сотрудника за неисполнение приказа
course, where
конечно где
not in Russia, but where and before there is quite no
не в россии а где а перед довольно нет
opposition in Russia in general, the death penalty
оппозиции в россии вообще смертная казнь
is a
есть
man, what did you not go about
мужик ты о чем не шли по мой помощник
?  with respect, it
мощных 1александр еще надо с уважением
is decided to decide on the
ставится решится к
victorious you are not the country
побеждающий вы не стране
in fact, so to speak, it’s not at all anywhere,
по факту это так скажем не вообще никуда
if you don’t fight anything at all,
не если не воевать вообще ничего ходу
so why did you climb,
так а зачем ты лез
you know how I don’t know the order, maybe I
ну знаешь как бы я не знаю приказ может
myself served correctly before, I don’t
и раньше сам служил правильно не
understand what feeds, see how I  a person with a
пойму что подачи смотри я как человек с
legal education
юридическим образованием
I’m trying to understand you tes belly and urgently
пробую тебя понять тэсу живот и срочку
served in the Russian army well, I
служил в российской армии ну я давал
swore an oath to whom the
присягу кому
Russian Russian si quieres yes, and here it
российской российские si quieres д а тут
turns out that you are following the orders
получается что ты исполняешь приказы
of some incomprehensible chumaks who do not
каких-то непонятных чумаков которые не
belong to the armed forces of the Russian
относятся к вооруженным силам российской
Federation, how does the
федерации как это
doctor do it this way  well, it turns out,
доктору так получаются ну-ка получается
and
а
if they give the order to kill Putin,
если они дадут приказ убить путина
it’s us, in general, it’s ohr  but if now, probably, the company will give you an order to kill Putin or Lavrov or Kadyrov, which is definitely better to fill up this green on Kadyrov's question, I read all Russians immediately shrinks like this in the middle because he is waiting for an order from Putin if Putin now gives the order to fill up all Ukraine something it’s littered and I’m in God’s eyes these moments are cool and in short, they’re just mooing, we would have captured you, we just need to wait for the order until we called, leaned on cues, then screams their appearance was like a game of poles sunk eat or drink water than she screams everything to disassemble you check an order to take it and take it for real until it doesn’t receive from they expect from you there will be no trace here it turns out putin came near Kyiv he was kicked out of there from the serpentine island they kicked out Kherson already there and you are carrying and he still doesn’t give an order then we don’t really understand why to come near Kyiv already stand near Kyiv and leave in order to later receive an order to go again
это мы их вообще это охрана
to Kyiv, I’m now that the authorities don’t understand this, here you are as a military man, so you’re like a mercenary, tell me what is the logic they threw they threw a lot of people like you so that they don’t die so then they got the stars dumped and now they are waiting for their own order, when Ukraine has strengthened more than it’s funny you’re with us and iris, so you have to understand can I’m not a military strategist, I don’t understand why then it was necessary to go there to Kyiv to put a huge number of our elite units of such mercenaries a cocktail in order to then run away from there and now tell what muscles if there is someone’s order no, we took orders, but there is no order, yes, you understand that I am looking again from my point of view, I am not a military expert, an analyst, but I think that if Russia could have implemented it in the first weeks about it, it would have it didn’t pull for a month a month here now we are now we decide to conquer it is clear that Russia did not have enough strength for Ukraine it was Zelensky who wanted so much as Zelensky on the  filming,
зеленский на съемках
well, I already wanted with Ali to make Russia
ну так уже хотел с али чтобы россия что
want to
захотел
start a war, how can I look this
развязать войну как же я загляну этот
guy, it’s you who have been preparing for this for 8 years,
мужик это вы же к этому 8 лет готовились
meaning we have been preparing since 91,
смысле готовим с 91 года готовились у
we have been preparing the armed forces, developing, we
нас вооруженной силы развиваешься у нас
can attack any country is
могут напасть любая страна готовится
preparing, what does it have to do with 8 years  and it’s not important that you
при чем тут 8 лет и не мышь на важно
filed a mouse, but you attacked us, let’s you
подали а вы на нас напали давайте ты
get caught again
сейчас меня еще раз попадешься еще
now, tell me about it, tell me now,
расскажем на давай щас расскажи
do you want to read books somewhere where
ты хочешь где-то книжки почитать где
it’s written how to tell Zelensky’s assistant the
написано как рассказать помощнику
creeper’s tail I’m not laughing at you here is a
криперы хвост не смеюсь тебя здесь
joke of what I wanted and reality with a
прикол чего хотела и реальность с
feeling  humor is bad at
чувством юмора плохо до
home you lie
дома лежишь
rest at home or in a hotel
отдых у дома или в гостинице
such a small hut
хатка такая небольшая
did not earn money
не заработал
for work and where did these three close mercenaries earn money
за работу и куда деньги денег
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
earned by the
заработал
approach of
этих троих близкие наемников подходом по
making money and obviously a change house, we won’t
заработку денег и явно бытовку то не об
surprise them in line for 1 dozen and where he
удивим их очередь на 1 десяток и куда он
wants  this money is earned money she is
хочет эти деньги заработанные деньги она
puffed up and so one more I will
напыщенные вверх и так еще одна
get in short where the strategist can withstand
раздобуду короче куда устоит стратег
financially they want to virtually contribute to the
финансово им виртуально вклада хочет
look
напишите
somewhere back to back financially investing
куда-то впритык финансово инвестирование
I’ll tell you where he can get his money
скажу куда он может свои деньги
I want to invest that this one is in Gazprom shares lining
хочу вложить что этот в акции газпрома
up now it’s fashionable
подклады сейчас это модно
I throw a
я кидаю
good one on a good strategy and
хороший на хорошей стратегии так и
they
сделали
did this one and like a lawyer
вот этот и как типа юрист это
advised me that you advised where the
посоветовал мне что посоветовал вы куда
money is already but to you  to a Russian bank and
деньги уже но тебе в российский банк а
then when they burned down to make it even
потом когда они сгорели чтобы было еще
more painful, you realized
больнее ты понял
that you were
что ты
killing people
убивал людей
mediocrely, you didn’t even come in here, why did
бездарно даже не зашел тут почему
citizens, well, like the rotation wanted how
граждан ну и тип ротацию хотел как
to earn money for children, the money was gone,
деньги заработать детей деньги пропали
can you
ты
imagine how
представляешь как бы
insulting it is,
обидно
but you can’t understand one of his laces
но тебе не понять один из кружева него
Ivolgin  you sit with some foreigners of the
иволгин с иностранными
essence of the issue and don’t
некоторых сути вопроса сидишь и не
understand how it is to come to a foreign country
понять как это приходить в чужую страну
and kill people there
и убивать людей там
they start to attack him like
они начинают нападать ему как смотри
this one again but you drop it attacked or you
этот еще раз но выронишь напали или ты
came from Voronezh here
из воронеже приперся сюда
explain I do
объясним не понимаю
n’t understand you don’t understand I really don’t understand now
не поймешь я реально не понимаю вот
look through you must  yes, look like a
смотрите через должен да вот смотри как
lawyer, I look here in Ukraine on legally
юрист я смотрю тут украине на юридически
there are some houses of the Russian Federation  they came from the Russian Federation and
какие-то домики из российской федерации
attacked Ukraine, and not vice versa,
приехали напали в украину а не наоборот
where is Ukraine attacking that you are
то где же украина нападает что вы
attacking neighboring countries,
нападаете на соседние страны
but such tie
но такие врезки
-ins like Zelinsky’s assistant are somehow
типа помощник зелинского ли как-то
explained to
объясняются
relatives by multiple cassette recorder Orestovich and they
родным кратно кассетник орестович а
fired me, they appointed me to more wisely,
уволили меня назначили на более мудро
I say, well,
говорю ну
you would have it all like that
вы бы это все так а
but even to me, why do you
вот мне даже а вот зачем ты украину
choose ukraine in chat roulette
выбираешь в чат-рулетке
why do you choose ukraine in chat roulette i
зачем ты украина выбираешь чат-рулетке
want to listen to their opinion, that is, what kind of
хочу послушать их мнение то есть а какое
opinion is this feeling and you want
мнение такое чувство и ты хочешь у тебя
somewhere in your soul were you understand that you have
где-то в душе были ты понимаешь что ты
done bad and  business and now you want
наделал плохих и дела и теперь хочешь
to somehow find excuses for your deeds
как-то найти оправдания своим делам
no why is that all for me but something that’s
нет почему мне все а что то что вот что
what you feel from him even from it’s
такое чувствуешь от него даже от это
interesting that for how long the
интересно то что за сколько время
conversation hasn’t even switched from
разговора вот и даже не переключил из
it means you are so curious it became
значит тебе это так любопытно стало
curious of course yes  I don’t come here
любопытно конечно да я сюда прихожу не
to switch in order
для того чтобы переключаться для того
to communicate with people a
чтобы с людьми общаться
lot is offered,
много предложен
but it turns out look you came to kill
но получается смотри ты приходил убивать
people in Ukraine
людей в украине
now you choose Ukraine  and you look at how
теперь выбираешь украину и смотришь как
they regen and
они реген и
don’t understand
не понимать
you choose ukraine and watch how people
ты выбираешь украину и смотришь как люди
from ukraine react to you yes the
из украины реагируют на тебя да
girl writes to
девушка пишет на
[music]
[музыка]
married
женатый
no even right because it’s better
нет даже правильно потому что лучше и
for mercenaries to die on
так умирать
their own
наемникам самостоятельно
you know that the child, too, mother doesn’t
ты знаешь что ребенку тоже мама не
say something  then there dad was a mercenary,
сказать что-то там папа был наемником
it’s even a shame, of course, and
это стыдно даже конечно а
who your dad was
у тебя папа кем был
the same
такой же
well, but look
ну а вот смотри
you of the Russian Federation you have huge
вы российской федерации у вас огромные
reserves of oil, gas of the mind
есть запасы нефти газа ума
with a piece of iron of the skull, according to the news, he transmitted something
с железкой черепа по новостям передал то
that would prohibit the supply of fuel to this
что запретит подачу топлива в этот
Ukraine, the abyss where the supply of fuel came from
украину бездна откуда подачу топлива
Russia,
россии
this is him, so we have Europe’s call to gasoline
это он так что у нас европы вызов бензин
, but at first we are supplying me with
на же перекрыли сначала мы навина мне
fuel and
поставляете топлива и
fuel and gas, we will soon cut off gas too,
топлива и газ скоро перекроем тоже газ
we in Europe will buy
мы в европе покупаем
it soon in Europe, he will close the dish, this
скоро его в европе он закроет блюдо это
is for you fairy tales like
это вам сказочки типа
you need to sound personally yours, but inside  pens
надо sound лично ваш а вот внутри ручки
I'm like I'm leading to what Russia is
я я как я к чему веду что россия такая
such a rich country has oil and gas, then
вроде богатая страна имеет нефтегаза то
diamonds are sold to the whole of Europe, so the
алмазы предмет продает всей европе так
syrup pays her grandmas so how much  you
сиропа платит ей бабки так почему ты в
live in Russia so poorly in such
россии живешь вот так бедно в таких
conditions, I see the story like this and you still
условиях история вижу так и еще
have to work as mercenaries
приходится тебе работать наемникам
why do you live in but it’s worse for me than,
почему ты живешь в но мне же хуже чем
for example, a
например
guy lives in a small Czech Republic
парень живёт в маленькой чехии
who buys gas from Russia then
которая покупает газку у россии то
takes your grandmother I
забирает твоей бабки
understood the
понял
glider was at two
планерный был у двух
started
началась
interesting turned into a counterattack so it
интересная перешел в контратаку так
began this is my love for 1 from my
началась такова моя у люблю на 1 от моих
favorite rights why people in the Czech Republic live
любимых прав почему люди в чехии живут
psychologists from epson you don’t live about
психологи от epson не живешь тоже об
chocolate either but somehow not like that, that is, to
шоколаде но каком-то не таком то есть ко
me but I adore 2 thousand peasants and
мне но я обожаю 2 тыс я крестьян и
start pleasantly why  such a
начинают приятненько почему такая
big great shorter country rich from
большая великая короче страна богатая от
and shorter with such a sofa
и короче таким диваном
who, like no one else, would go to where and pulls out money
кто как никто бы кому идут где и деньги
from oil and gas diamonds,
с нефтегаза алмазов
why can’t you like cherry
вытаскивает а почему не можешь как вишня
information of course iterations, look, I
информацию конечно интераций смотри я
’ll tell you yes, Putin and his entourage, the
тебе расскажу да путин и его окружение
oligarchs climb and grandmas on yachts,
олигархи забираются и бабки на яхты
palaces and  villas are like a little money thrown
дворцы и виллы как немножко бабок кидают
at these military campaigns types
на вот эти военные кампании типы
voltmeter Shabane gave you a handout and you
вольтметр шабане тебе дали подачку и ты
went to kill people and dock for yourself
пошел убивал людей и док сам ради
in order for Putin and the oligarchs to
ради того чтобы путин и олигархи
keep their yacht palaces and so on,
сохраняли свои дворцы яхты и так дальше
instead of this money from oil and gas
вместо того чтобы эти деньги с нефтегаза
going to you by which relatives mom dad
шли тебе коими родственникам маме папе
you live poverty touching always
ты живешь нищета трогательную всегда
touching you live in poverty you
трогательно ты живешь в нищете ты
laugh as a defensive reaction but you
смеешься как защитная реакция но ты
understand that with such resources why
понимаешь что с такими ресурсами почему
some emirates live like death in
какие-то эмираты смертью так живут в
chocolate and you
шоколаде а ты
run to years discounts lead
беги к лет скидки лид
could still be old well so maybe for
еще мог уже старый ну так возможно для
you old you how old you are
тебя старый тебе сколько
20 22
20 22
almost twice as old .
почти в два раза старше .
and now you eat now he and
и вот и ты питаешься сейчас он и
bite not bite I will throw into your
кусаться не кусаться я тебе в мозг
brain such grains that
закидаю такие зёрна которые со временем
will sprout or rot over time, there are simply different brains in
прорастут или сгниют просто есть мозги
some brains the grains of communes he does
разные некоторых мозгах зерна гмин он не
not germinate and for some reason you are a shirt
которых прорастают и ты зачем-то рубашка
or
или
because I like shirts sometimes a
потому что мне нравятся рубашки иногда
t-shirt  dress i like jack t-shirt
футболка одеваю мне нравится футболка
&amp; for example i don't like shirts and
jack &amp; например не люблю рубашки и
t-shirts i like yes and the same so
футболки люблю да и такой же так вот
look
смотри
now you are now talking to yourself
ты сейчас сейчас разговоре сам это и
and you can't deny this dacha more and more
ничего не может и все больше отрицать
but when we switch off you will
этой даче но когда мы отключаемся ты
think anyway but really if
задумаешься все равно а реально если
russia has so many grandmas  gets crazy from oil
россия столько бабок получает от нефти
gas hovered over the whole of Europe sell
газа ума зависли над всей европе продают
gas can you imagine so many millions of
газ представляешь столько миллионов
people buy gas from russia
людей покупает газ у россии
but where does all this money from this gas go
но куда девается все эти деньги с этого
why for example in this
почему например в этом
standard moment
стандартный момент
you have to answer why you run [ __ ] so
надо отвечать почему бежишь говне так
despite the fact that the
несмотря на то что
cross on which you are who  writes
крест на которую ты то кто пишет
about the
о
moderators
девалась модераторы
put likes and
ставьте лайки и
let's turn around what will I
давайте повернемся какие будут я
consist of did not on the list
состоит из did not on the list
posner  it’s not wide and
познер не широко и
such a thought, alla dialogue,
такая думка алла диалог
in principle, yes information, try a
в принципе да информации попробовать
blow, it’s nothing there, a strong magician
удар это ничего там сильный маг и из
and what lurked from the pipe, why do you live
трубы таилась какие а почему ты живешь
with me, people love the runner, you throw it
ко мне люди люблю бегун им за кидаешь
there, and there it turns on a bundle of composition
туда , и там включается пучкова состава
starting
начиная
from the leg blowing today so today  we
от нога дующий сегодня так сегодня у нас
have over and
есть над и
ukraine today on and in front of the color floating
украины сегодня на и перед цвет плавать
on the skin on my films we will guess
на коже на мои фильмы будем загадывать
not the way to the date the sound of the tsar
не путь до даты звук царь
on the honorary normal sound on everyone’s
на почётче нормальный звук у всех по
head write write whether the normal
голову напишите напишите ли нормальный
sound changed you hear normally normal
звук меняли слышно нормально нормально
miracle and
чудо и
[music]
[музыка]
today I am again china  from the wedge pro and
сегодня я снова china от клина про и
humate moves but every air we will
гумат ходы но каждому эфире будем
put them off as sincere as peter and
откладывать их искренны как петр и
wet and we had poland food without
мокрые и у нас была польша питание без
google the river grass was visible for you about
гугла река трава была видна за ты про
chickens authoritatively who already know and even for
кур властно которые уже знают и даже за
crying and give another food from the corner
плач и давайте другой питанием с угла
let them still deliver  to
пусть таки доставьте к
great mouth and words china rule wing
великому рот и слова china правило крыло
name what year
называешь каком году
milk declared independence
молоке провозгласила независимость
write what year dog county
напишите на каком году собаки округу
declared independent write  sew how
провозгласила не зависит напишите как
you lessons paid voted for lying
вам уроки плачено проголосовано за
down
ложится
once once once
раз раз раз
normal sound
нормальный звук
by 2020 I ask the
к 2020 прошу
church to 92 of those children
церковь до на 92 тех детей
blacker scatter and the
blacker разброс и
result is
результат
right and right kind of face from
так и правильно вид лица от
cool in the ninety-fifth lesson duck
классная в девяносто пятом уроке дак у
you have a Rogin blog there for two
вас там рогинский блог по два
fists otherwise in words  Czechoslovaks and
кулака иначе по слова чехословаки и
powerful 90 spend a company of fans divided
властных 90 тратим роте фане разделилась
into the Czech Republic from the club than absolutely
на чехию из клуба чем абсолютно
sports rnb from a quiet stand of
спортивном rnb с тихой стану
mutual claims somehow for the good of which it is
взаимных претензий как-то блага чего
entertaining and to the nozzles exploded there
занимательно и к взрывалась насадок там
on the territory of the vinnik so
по территории винник настолько откуда
fragmentary and in the ninety-third lesson in the
отрывочны и в девяносто третьем уроке на
third lesson Ukraine Czech Republic
третьем уроке утроилось украина чехия
Ukraine tripled  handbags
украина сумочек
5th and
5-е и
let's continue continue to go through
давайте продолжим продолжим пройти
food without google
питанием без гугла
develop at the largest places on watchin
развить при наибольших местах на watchin
name the three
назовите три
largest cities in the words of
самых больших города словах
tradition to attack and educational this
традиции напасть и воспитательным этом
that there in north korea started there on
что там у северной кореи начали там на
traffic up to five hundred information
трафике до пятиста информации лизнула
licked spam will distinguish again by just
заспамлю отличат еще раз по просто
name three  largest city on the
назовите три самых больших город на
tab for two or three largest places
вкладке на две-три наибольших места
sl  ova than in one and by type it
слова чем в одном и по видам не
won’t try
попробует
so only bodybuilding seems 90 the
так только культуризмом кажется 90
other two you form contagious
другие два ты заразным формируем
[music]
[музыка]
here to name read the extra length in the
вот назвать почитать лишняя длина в
square of lessons for 1
квадрате уроков за 1
time
раза раз
one
одно
here on click 1 session for a minute of
вот на нажмите 1 сессия на минуту
craters
кратеров
there is no sin maybe 90 friend was accepted
нет греха может 90 другу была принята
the declaration is simple in ukraine so there the
декларация просто в украине так там
horse's mouth is 6 90 porsche
рот лошади 6 90 porsche
normally
нормально
just water.  like this, let’s
просто вода . вот так давай
later look to be bigger, strive for the
позже вид быть на бильше стремись к
words rank, this is
слова чин это
bratislava borscht and and the beach of skins, this is God,
братислава борщец и и пляж кож это бог
it seems to us Schengen for and hide bitterness,
нам кажется шенгена за и прячь горечи
hides something
прячет так-то
Ukrainian, this is a great region of that
украинский это отличный регион тот
territory, lived and the vowel of the Ukrainians
территории д проживал и гласная украинцы
Quina lightning works somehow  so
квина молнии трудов еще как-то так
great to increase come wiki the same
отлично увеличить прийти вики же
values somehow hiding the mashkants the investor wr
значения как-то машканты прячущего
tes where do you get the patience I sell ukra
инвестор пишет откуда вы берете терпение
ne and
я продаю
just falls out o
украины и просто
the rocks of the form I sit and you and china singi
выпадает из пород вида сижу и у вас и
g for is just my fault on th
китай пения за является просто моему
stick in the morning and enough of us logs praha
вину на стике утром и достаточно нас
rati
логов
lava belgrade praha  and belgra
прага братислава белград прага и белград
it's different other countries of the
это разные другие страны
panel so
панели так
[music]
[музыка]
ok and guy danda find to vichy often
окей и парень данда найти к виши часты
didn't find those icons ours and
не нашли те икона наши и
ours aspire to
наша стрематься
lenses nonchalant analysis
линз беспечный анализ
we'll talk about 1 per fleece they say how we'll
мы поговорим об 1 на ватку мол как
try a bomb to give ideas and
попробуем бомба давать идеи и
try water on armored personnel carriers and
попробуем вода на бтр и
infantry fighting vehicles and  daiki
бмп и daiki
words words such a hammer budget and how I
слова слова такое молот бюджет и как
counted
рассчитывал
on yours from Estonia, well, daddy I want this
на твою из эстонии ну папаша хочу этот
boy, these facts are Ukrainian and
мальчик еще вот эти факты украинская и
it would be sweet to sell to my mother  at the cross
сбывать к мама сладко бы счету у креста
was look for a battle wat of course Russian,
был ищи battle wat конечно российскую
so which of the Russians listens so the
так вот кто из россиян слушает так
Ukrainian language is closer in vocabulary to the
украинский язык по лексике ближе к
Slovak language than the mug, it seems like
словацкого языку чем кружка вроде как
they tell us there against the ideal
нам говорят там против идеальным этом
one people, but the words from food to
один народ так но слова от еды к
Ukrainian are closer than Russian Ukrainian
украинскому ближе чем русский украинской
68 skyscrapers in the back  and lots of the then 68
68 высотки в спину и lots of the то 68
percent of the
процентов
local pilaf is however in sweet languages
местных плов есть однако в сладком языки
ukrainian so it is not difficult for a Ukrainian to understand the words
и в украинском поэтому украинцу понять
k and copulate it is not d
слова к и совокупиться это
fficult and let's secrets and let's
несложно и давай тайны и
go home go who find kvesh
давай кальби дома перейдем кто найти
them find kvesh their momen
квеш их найти квеш их
sc &amp;
моменте
guess the melody so here let's porsc
sc&amp;t угадай мелодию так вот же давайте
e  and life, let's honor with cunningly at
porsche и быта давайте почтим с хитро
once the leprosy of the power of the
сразу проказам силы рача
rach buy taro repairing the oars watts
прикупить таро чиня весла ватт
translate this sentence into the Slovak
переведите это предложение словацкую
language
языка
[music]
[музыка]
for the clock of the brand nodded at and smoothly
ибо часы марки кивнул на и складно
former summary from somewhere
бывший откуда-то резюме
you who will understand them observe the
вы кто будете понимать них соблюдать
mind you yourself
разуме ты вы сами
will tell us the truth
нас правде
Latin because  behind the bush but hello and even a little
латинку из-за куста но алло да еще мало
sounds so we are afraid yes you seem so
звучит так мы боимся да ты похоже так
means Slovak every simple close to
значит словацко каждый простую близко до
not ours you are somewhere
не наш вы куда-то
and giving  hey, I’m sure that Masha’s initiative will be
и давай-ка я точно почином маша будет
so valuable in the tone of speed, the buzz from the plan is
такого ценная в тон спида гул от плана
so accessible right away, he’s sweet
так и доступны сразу мил он
words just like that, but on the
же слова просто так а на
keys, but according to you, the anchor is on you and
ключи но по вашим на вас дуку якорь и
where are you evil, finally, it means what the
куда это ты зло ваще он означает что
teacher means dexterous in the Slovak language
означает педагог ловок словацком языке
well, morning until morning, a washcloth of wounds and it’s
так утра до утра мочалка ранок и
right to look at it, because it’s tame to
правильно вид по ведь то ручных до
the point that the losses in the pirate and
дуслык то что утраты в пират так и
more
побольше
sleeping pills get Bogotá forecasts who
снотворным достать прогнозами боготу кто
can be seen further down the center of the ole bull shlyk and in
видно дальше центр шлык оле булл и в
Russia in the morning it’s also logical at the simulator and the
россии утра тоже логично у тренажера и
boolo scooters gave a cake 50 cool
було скутеров дал пирог 50 прикольный
buff
buff
oklick
oklick
maybe and who I think is even rich, you
авось и кого я думаю даже богата то
can see just the words
видно просто слова
which means to the word
что означает к слову
in Slovak it is in Slovak which
на словацким он на словацком языке что
means from the word
означает от слова
you and Italian came to say chiron
вас и итальянский пришли на скажет хирон
halvat drama Carpathians
халват драма карпаты
in English effect
на английском эффект
from tamiya firm
от фирмы tamiya
you are Ukrainian my daughter year one in
вы украинский мою дочь году один в
given Christmas time moves and Buddhism, so here’s the
данный святки ходы и буддизме так вот
serpent gorynych, while we’re
змей горыныч пока
well rebuffed, we’ll move on until less words
хорошо отпор переходим до меньше словах
lore
лоре
still means to be with
еще означает быть с
them in
ними на
position
позиции
, it was decided Slovak mine means to carry
было решено словацкий мой означает нести
the word
слово
ehad snake then
эхад змея потом им же
you study it
вы изучается
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
when they put the day on
когда ставят день
almost nothing I’m not angry at him sec
почти ничем не злюсь на него сек
essay kadyrbek so much miami may
очерка кадырбек так сильно майами мая
correct view see dota
правильная видповиди dota
dota on my correct centuries and thought and shock
dota на мои правильно века и дума и шок
from the father of the snake then adika
от отца змея то адика
not a single horse meat  viper to devour you, but
ни один конина гадюка вас пожрать это но
I love poetry, which means what
я стихи счет любви что означает чему
the viper is named, think up to the radish agate
названа гадюка прикиньте до радюк агат
snake, and so it called us
змея и вот называла у нас
cool
прикольно
amikacin and garik and e yaroslav chika you are
амикацин и гарика и е ярослав чика ты
stuffing on google student and that’s how the
начинкой на google ученик а вот так то
hose is
шланг
both rolling the hose
обе катя шланг
i.
т.е.
barricades ok crash until we swear further and
баррикады ok рухайся до ругаемся далее и
there is ethics and try to find vichy we
есть этика и постараться найти к виши у
have a potter
нас поттера
dead you glue learned from the conditions we guess
дохну вы клеите узнали от условий гадаем
I’m loading here from the word imola shop
я со слова прогружается здесь лавочка
how this word is
как это слово
translated facial from which language what it
переводится facial от кого языка что оно
means that means exiled to the universe
означает то означает сослал до universe
I’m still a god  understands their blackness, I know the
я таки бог понимает их черноту знаю
hose hoses,
шланг шланги
which means half a year for contractions, you can
что означает полгода на на схватки можно
give even cups, they say, the floor is a shame
дай хоть и чашки мол этаж позор
on the valuable alba alba alba
на ценная alba alba alba
soles, then they write on two
подошвах потом пишут на два
types of attention and lifeview, yes, on the door ipa
типа внимание и lifeview да по door ipa
evening you have
вечор у вас
a shame these are the days of May, take into account
на позор это дни мая во внимание
the max  it is necessary to issue a hug
на макса необходимо выдать обнимаем
in the morning of the light bulb for later and that you who have
утра лампочки на позже и что вы кто
been
бывал
behind the cordon and a miracle you have grown up medicine of the
за кордоном и чудо ты подрос медицина
case
дела
okay allata chance
окей аллата шанса
blow
удар
blow from visible yes it means sent
удар от видно да это означает прислал
another means the boiler
еще означает котла
means once the words of the excavation of whom the
означает когда-то слова котлован кого
label and
ярлыка и
50 or even lessons on the red tip  my
50 или даже уроки на красный кончик моя
come and new
приехать и новый
prophecy different
prophecy иной
come on I think me from the very peak
давайте-ка я думаю меня с самого пиковая
sabotage to cheaters sneezing for a
диверсии к читерам начихать на
thousand means refusal but but words and the
тысячу означает отказ но но слова и
sea
морем
me at the
меня на
next one I
очередном я
appoint a mouth buggy
назначаю рот глючили
furious
разъяренный
knurled for spending on
накатаны на траты на
various
различные
they just thought your pack I
они просто подумала ваша свора я
break the batch for
разбейся
him and left the
ему батчата и налево
new products can
новинок можно
I have various
я различные
alla batik clear and nato
алла батик четкому и нато включена
protection of the future is on
защита будущем на
sophia and was betrayed part ticked and and
так и предан был тикало часть и и
cause Kim offense the same  chat is
вызывать ким обиду же чат
prevented by the words in these we will be written by a
предотвращаются слова в этих нам напишут
company commander and two large ones, so at least we start
ротный и два крупных так хоть начинаем
from there simply is no such word
от просто нет такого слова
which means a tattoo in sending a dictionary and my
что означает тату в слать словарь и мою
these gifts are a series of this
эти подарком череда это
type of attention to various gases,
типа внимание различных газов нас тут
this laptop started us here
начал этот ноутбук
so you say the fortuneteller was so great and to
так ты скажи гадалка так велик был и к у
we are being
нас проводится
woods and at all and the
вудса и вовсе и
god wolf
бог волк
wolf
волк
action and lying around
экшон и поваляюсь
me recorded cycle ala cooli series 2 3
меня записано цикла ала кулли серию 2 3
hours let's try step east the
час давайте попробуем шагу востоке
basis of gurk
основу гурк
which means the word is
что означает слово
simple but here is epub
просто но вот epub
well yes orbit mouse combine in days and
ну да орбита мышь комбинируем в дни и
stalls show means
ларьки шоу значит
excel tires means bara bere
excel утомляет означает bara bere
peak enemy
вершина враг
both bottle stop and
оба бутылка стоп и
from where, according to the speaker,
откуда по словам спикера
agrh, well, come on, what I remember
агрх ну так давай что я памятаю
incorrectly wrote a couple will be  Are you
неправильно написал пара будет вы
ready to get
готовы получать
mara and
мара и
bedside tables, which we say to the top Irina,
тумбочек какую мы говорим верху ирина
so we have
так вот у нас есть
Pimanov’s hands, there are news riding
пиманов руки есть новости верховые
upstairs in Minsk, I’m hanging out at KVN games, but there
наверху минске я торчу игр квн а ведь
was a city, and someone is gypsy,
был город а кто-то цыганские
so let’s go back to our
значит так и давайте вернемся до наших
shop
цех
1sk in the new century of May
1ск новом веке мая
not  could volost
не могли волостных
as such honestly
как такового честно чая
Slovak tea can Abdullaeva
словацкой могут абдуллаева
and
и
clubs thinks with PPS fashionable look but this is a
клубы думает с ппш модный look но это
chance and those who think pancake alloy without
шанс а те кто думаю блин сплава без
unanimously I will still surprise you
единогласно я вас еще удивлю
the angry panel will please and on it the windows are not a
панель angry порадует и на ней окна не
whim of starvation a friend of clay learns to
прихоть измор другу глины научается
aim doctors under poppy no one you  above the
нацелил врачи под мак никто вы выше
phenomena of pan &amp; andre only shields
феномены pan &amp; andre только щитами
decides maybe the date yes it just doesn’t
решает может быть дата да так просто не
repent over it
кается над
means smart smart
означает смарт смарт
but read the
но читать
text online
текст оnline
at a time obeys to find the kvesh is revealed
за раз подчиняется найти квеш выявляется
in the trash of hell many figures of the phrase and
в хлам адский многие деятели фразы и и
and where are you the key over to jump again
в куда это вы ключ над прыгнуть снова
tissue language there are whole  phrases that
ткани языке есть целые фразы которые
consist exclusively of
состоят исключительно из
according to and you will find the phrase
согласно и найдешь ведома фраза
cppk in the top of
цппк в топ перекладач его тут написан
translations it is written here who will translate what is written in this
кто переведёт что написано в этом
sentence
предложении
is  the tongue twister is Czech and Slovak, it
это скороговорка чешская и словацкая она
seems to sound the same in Czech in Slovak
вроде и на чешском на словацком
from the sampler of Perikles st and the score is in sight here, and the
с пробника перикла ст и счет тут виду а
god of Pericles knocks at least
бог перикла стучат по крайней словах
try if you can’t Perry
попробуйте если не можете перри
translate this whole sentence, try
перевести все это предложение попробуйте
translating individual words
перевести отдельные слова
into prizes
на призы
and
и
let’s 2 thousand
давайте 2 тыс
clearly joking for  sketch i we
явно постебался для наброска я мы
horseshoe scored cheese she is such a phrase and
подкова набрал сыр она такая фраза и
cool you hit and the world put your finger
крутую ты попал и world просунуть палец
down the throat of
в горло
pula kumara [ __ ] you us holiday here are the
пулы кумара хуй ты нас праздник вот
pictures so that's what the ring is or
фотки так вот что такое перстень или
so why its 20 but because the steam style of the
так чего его 20 а потому что пар стиль
dachshund was
таксы было
suppressed to become switch fingers
подавлено становиться коммутатор пальцы
and
и
think
думаю
enough of their noise and pike to him channels
хватит их шум и щука ему каналах
leaving
покидающие
naked don’t go with if we shower 20
голых не иди своей с если мы душ 20
just can you argue on it funny
просто можем ли ты спорить на ней смеш
wild and
диким и
print about the magazines of the days you
печатаем о журналах дней ты
said the Ukrainian can open up to part
сказал украинскую могут открыть до часть
on the creak-creak
на скрип-скрип
the floors came to
пришло полы
me and to this but  what can you find
я и к этому а вот чё как на можно найти
if you can see the crack on the
если ты видны крэк на
flight in Lithuanian finger writes hq too
полет на литовском перста пишет hq тоже
tank and liquid gas and squeeze
бачка и ликвидной газика и сдавливают
this hello old could
данную привет давних мог
panda is not a beginner 20 the thought is already bursting three times
панда не новичка 20 дума не три раза уже
already these same ones you exceed
пышет вот эти самые вами превышать
spam barely a scan from show-off to the chat and
спамят едва скан из понты в чат и данным
thus torture ok
тем самым пыток ok олег шак думаю
we have so few things,
так мало у нас вещи
damn it, it’s even in our eyes about
блин она даже на глаза о
soon ending from the right
скоро [__] от права
who 2 kovalev can coach we’ll
кто 2 ковалев может коучем доедим
finish the ideas the
идейки
founders right
основатели право
although we also have a boy from tess
хотя по у нас же и мальчика из тесс у
we crossed damask on
нас булат скрестив на
we forget almost we can already these
мы забываем почти мы уже можем эти
other phrases so he
другие фразы так
knows them  they sawed the barrel,
знает их пилили ствол ак а
well, try the magnets just blink, they could
ну попробуйте магниты просто blink могли
go to jail for it, the
за это в тюрьму
Slovak doctors, not
словацком врачи не
the salon
вот салона
after going to the barrels to
после ехать к бочкам
fix it, maybe Islam, we live in the
исправлять могут быть ислама к мы живем
pores that we had before the final of the cycle, but here are the
поры что у нас было до финала цик а вот
notes of the twin for you, here is the Czech Republic spool
нотки тебе близнеца вот чехии spool
active e in new  free sad
активных е в нови свобод грустный
smartphone
смартфоном
3d
3d
lie down with chris brown pinned tail to
приляг with chris brown прижаты хвост к
vain I don't know citizens and foliage on about the types of
зря не знаю граждан и листва на о видах
mos2 books these signs at the expense of the needle to you the same
mos2 книг эти знаки на счет иглы вам же
food and I'm glad to the contributor tun seems bad
еда и я рад вкладчику тун кажется дурно
earth hole y
земля дыру у
turn me down to the bloody past and try that through the program the
убавь и пытаться что через программу
sorcerer yes,
чародей да а
well, let's figure out
ну давайте разгадаем разгадывать
who treated the fish like that through the grass,
кто обращалась так рыбку через траву
someone will think for a moment, you know the
кто-то миг будет давайте подумает знаете
Ukrainian sea and the pilaf brush in the game
украинский море и кисть плова в игре
you are here, I'm cool and ashvil instant 6 through the
тебя тут я крут и эшвиль миг 6 через
grass of the pipe
траву трубы
right churches and
правильно церкви и
then cry through the grass
потом крик через траву
ponds after all beards
пруды все-таки бороды
you because you were missing and separated
ты так как была на хватает и разлучены
yes and pdc then to think about r&amp;d
да а pdc то чтобы подумать об r&amp;d
is on the doll
находится на куклу
let's share the
давайте поделимся
cob to the door
початок до дверь
thyristor
тиристор
so why am I writing parts well soon could
так почему я пишу части ну скоро мог ее
wash it off and deciphered it  in reality, prices will
смывать и расшифровал это реально цены
come up there and over there, they will
там и вон придумают
sort out the activity of feeds when he farted
сортируют активность кормов когда пукнул
3 through 3 at the line, it’s pretty
3 через 3 у черты довольно
wild and swarming, you can find empty clicks
диким и кишел можно пустых кликов найти
more often as silently, although we have
почаще как беззвучно хотя у нас
goals, we have a tribute to the Slovak
цели у нас дань словацкой
logic saw,
пила логики
yes, a ram, this grain is absolutely right, so
да баран это зерно абсолютно верно так
we have already guessed the
мы разгадали уже
grain
зерно
nur  but I expelled and then
нур но я изгнал и то
found understands from stone wisdom the whole
нашли понимает из каменных мудрости весь
dozen live for
десятка проживаете за
that it will come out of the butt and you are used to the
то это выйдет приклада и ты привыкла в
rank or you  translate by translator or do you
не то вы переводите переводчиком или вы
know,
знаете а
well, let's parse the words to a friend
ну давайте разбором слов другу
before
до
first pudge this is that
сперва pudge это та та
bunch of
куча
bruce about genies this quit from the cob
брюс о джиннах этой quit с початку
grain errors chroot grain and
зерно ошибки chroot зерна а
didn’t guess super cool
не догадалась супер круто
right
верно
because from the usual glory and to Bukovina, the
ведь с привычных славы и до буковинских
Russian sea is
российский море
proud to rule the word insidiously
горд правят word коварно
on
на
and
и
came out and jester
вышел и шут
turkey
турция
author
автор
i over pray liquidity got a
я над молитесь ликвиды got a
equal jude i can not at the peak of flowers
равен джуд я не может на пике цветы
prominent and domineering from the project yes we
видных и властного из проекта да у нас
get the
получается
truth of the second halves of the ritku to the
правда вторых половинок ритку к
perfect typo of the streams knows
идеальному опечатку потоков лучше знает
me better for and
меня за и
fodder and also go out 3 trick on the grass
кормов и выходят также 3 тpюк нa в траву
from the cob of a left-hander, a
с початка левши
printout was bathed in a harvest of grain, this
распечатку купнулся жменю зерна этот у
we spent, we floated boots, we
нас провели мы ботинки всплывать мы
can, as if growling from strength due to
можем будто рычание от силы из-за грибы
John’s mushrooms and hunger, but what’s the meaning, well, what’s the
джона и голод но и чем смысл ну а в чем
meaning of
смысл
tongue twisters there a and b were sitting on a pipe, and
скороговорок там а и б сидели на трубе а
if it fell, the quarter would be gone  on a 3-bet
упала бы пропала квартал то на 3-бет или
or what is the point Sasha walked along the highway and sucked
в чем смысл шла саша по шоссе и сосала
total, the same vanossgaming butt, the
тотальное тому же vanossgaming приклад
score may seem to have a sense on purpose,
счет может будто и есть у смысла нарочи
not in the sense of a wiki, they
не в виде смысле вики
look
заглядывают
sad  glorify and the sea
грустный славят и море
cn dress such a collapse you were
сп одеваюсь такая развала вам
honored so to visit 0 to 215 kiki
сподобилась так на посетит 0 до 215 кики
you thought they really were able to by the window were
вы задумал они и вправду окном смогли на
honored 10 cool raise us you
сподобилась 10 прикольно поднимай нас ты
and develop
и развивай
I thought wisdom for
я думал мудрость для
someone
кого-то
like the pinnacle of philosophical views of the date
типа вершина философских воззрений даты
we can remove this
можем удалить эти
watch philip
часы philip
I’ll show you before 200 ml hellish
я тебя покажите раньше 200 мл адский
section of the molag there is Ukraine again without a
участке молаг есть украины снова без
shaft of dreams alive the frame of the doctor’s tunic was it
валу сны alive рамка кителе врача ли
possible to aim for the estuary Bulo
можно было цель лимана було
with
с
220 faq
220 faq
Yes,
да
okay it’s
окей
forgotten, so today we are repairing 50,000 rubles to my
забывается так вот же мы сегодня моему
visit
визиту
in the extinct and good
50000р чинят в потухших и це дуже добрые
15 more we load  when his battle in
15 еще мы нагружаем когда битва его на
our territories he lived a lot of food and go
наших территорий куча еду жил и пойти на
to help otherwise he loves hp but they
это помощь иначе любит hp но ведь они
found it thinks the arches of the T-shirt well, but ours or
нашли думает арки майки ну а наш или
think the thread to the center with conclusions you
думаете нить к центра выводами ты так
because now the prophetic Oleg is going to take revenge on the
как ныне сбирается вещий олег отмстить
unreasonable Khazars through the chelik of his horse the
неразумным хазарам через челик его коня
grass sprouted
проросла трава
filled  age-old itself for black, this is the
наполнял вековые самого для черного это
percentage of this shaft,
проц это вала
what is it like here, how are you, then how can this sing
до чего тут как ты тогда как этот петь
be fixed for right on 3 well, and then
можно крепить ля прямо по 3 ну а то и
who respecting else
кто уважая еще
we go  the reality is large and
мы идеальности е крупные и
intellectual, so are the necks and you
интеллектуальную так и шейки и вам будут
will not be idle, maybe Peter and why donate to me
им не праздный может и петр и на кой мне
3 of the Crimea to them it’s Victor’s numbers and Saturday
3 крыма им это викторов числа и суббота
at 9 tera by you covered us you crusts about
на 9 tera по вы укрыли мы ты корки про
can and
может и
will turn off the splash screen
отключит и заставочку
[music]
[музыка]
and I  forgot the most important thing to drag
и я забыл наиглавнейший натащить to
to become me102a for three days he has a
become me102a наш три дня у его на мину
cooler and a visual 2 on it who drips
кулер и визуальную 2 на ней кто дрипки
us david write who from which city
нас дэвид напишите кто из какого города
stella from laziness I watched our slim so that
стелла от лени я смотрел наш slim чтобы
I visualize you on the globe of the globe
я визуализировал тебе на глобусе земного
from where they looked at how wide
откуда нас смотрели на сколько широкая
ours is  geography
наша география
[music]
[музыка]
here
вот